Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Editorial Files, 1944-2016; 3
  - Micol Seigel, 2002-2008 (Box 327)
  - Mignolo, Walter: The Darker Side of Western Modernity, 2005-2011 (Box 247)
  - Mike May, 1991-1992 (Box 330)
  - Milagros Rena, 2000-2010 (Box 288)
  - Milanich, 2002-2009 (Box 309)
  - Milburn, 2006 (Box 300)
  - Milburn, Colin: Mondo Nano: Fun and Games in the World of Digital Matter, 2012-2015 (Box 361)
  - Miller, 1987 (Box 330)
  - Miller, 1995-1999 (Box 339)
  - Miller Monica, 2006-2010 (Box 309)
  - Miller, J.: Theory Now and Then, 1990-1992 (Box 210)
  - Miller, Marilyn G.; Tango Lessons, 2008-2014 (Box 114)
  - Miller, Marilyn G.; Tango Lessons; Permissions, 2010-2012 (Box 114)
  - Miller, Paul: From Revolutionaries to Citizens, 1997-2002 (Box 179)
  - Miller, Steven: Culture as Surveillance, 1992-1999 (Box 151)
  - Miller-Young, Mireille, 2007-2014 (Box 91)
  - Milt Sermett, 2001-2007 (Box 266)
  - Milton, Cynthia, ed.; The Arts of Truth-telling in Post-Shining Path Peru, 2011-2012 (Box 114)
  - Milton, Cynthia, ed.; The Arts of Truth-telling in Post-Shining Path Peru; Permissions, 2011-2012 (Box 114)
  - Mirowski, 2001-2004 (Box 275)
  - Mirzoeff, Nicholas: The Right to Look, 2010-2013 (Box 247)
  - Mirzoeff, Nicholas: Visual Rights, 2006-2011 (Box 247)
  - Mitchell, 2003 (Box 272)
  - Mitchell, 1992-1994 (Box 297)
  - Miyake, Akiko: Ezra Pound and the Mysteries of Love, 1988-1992 (Box 210)
  - Miyao, Daisuke; The Aesthetics of Shadow, 2011-2013 (Box 109)
  - Miyoshi and Harootunian: Postmodernism and Japan / SAQ, 1988-1995 (Box 303)
  - Miyoshi, Masao and Harootunian, Harry: Learning Places, 1999-2004 (Box 224)
  - Mizejewski (Box 339)
  - Mizejewski, Linda: Ziegfeld Girl, 1997-2003 (Box 151)
  - Moch, Leslie: The Pariahs of Yesterday, 2009-2011 (Box 253)
  - Modern Girls, 2003-2007 (Box 305)
  - Moer, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Molloy, Sylvia Irwin, Roberts: Hispanisms and Homosexualities, 1995-1999 (Box 179)
  - Molloy, Sylvia: Signs of Borges, 1990-1994 (Box 210)
  - Monisha Das Gupta, 2003-2005 (Box 282)
  - Monk, Daniel: An Aesthetic Occupation, 1997-2002 (Box 220)
  - Montag, Warren; Althusser and His Contemporaries, 2009-2013 (Box 109)
  - Montag, Warren; Althusser and His Contemporaries; Contract, 2012 (Box 109)
  - Montag, Warren; Althusser and His Contemporaries; Permissions, 2013 (Box 109)
  - Mookerjea, Soutayan and Imre Szeman, and Gail Farschou, 2007-2009 (Box 94)
  - Mookherjee, Nayanika: The Spectral Wound, File 1 of 2, 2011-2015 (Box 367)
  - Mookherjee, Nayanika: The Spectral Wound, File 2 of 2, 2004-2015 (Box 367)
  - Moon, 2005-2007 (Box 281)
  - Moon, Michael: A Small Boy and Others, 1997-1998 (Box 147)
  - Moon, Michael: Darger's Resources, 1997-2012 (Box 253)
  - Moore, 1996-2000 (Box 351)
  - Moore, Lisa: Dangerous Intimacies, 1994-1998 (Box 210)
  - Moore, Rachel: Savage Theory, 1997-2000 (Box 152)
  - Mora, Anthony: Border Dilemmas, 2004-2011 (Box 240)
  - Moraga, Cherrie: A Xicana Codex of Changing Consciousness, 2009-2012 (Box 240)
  - Morana, 2005-2008 (Box 293)
  - Moraña, Mabel, Enrique Dussel, and Carlos A. Jáuregui, edu; Coloniality at Large..., 2003-2008 (Box 96)
  - Moraña, Mabel, Enrique Dussel, and Carlos A. Jáuregui, edu; Coloniality at Large...; Contract, 2004-2007 (Box 96)
  - Moreiras, Alberto: The Exhaustion of Difference, 1995-2001 (Box 220)
  - Morris, 2005 (Box 272)
  - Morris, Meaghan; Creativity and Academic Activism, 2011-2012 (Box 109)
  - Morris, Rosalind: In the Place of Origins, 1995-2000 (Box 156)
  - Morton, 1980-1991 (Box 340)
  - Moses, Michael Valdez, 2000-2002 (Box 508)
  - Moss, Kary: Man-Made Medicine, 1993-1995 (Box 179)
  - Moten Fred (Box 334)
  - Mowitt, John: Percussion, 1995-2002 (Box 224)
  - Mowitt, John: The Genealogy of an Antidisciplinary Object, 1990-1993 (Box 131)
  - Moxey, Keith; Visual Time, 2010-2013 (Box 109)
  - Mrinalini Sinha, 2003-2006 (Box 283)
  - Mudimbe, V.Y.: Explorations in Postcolonial Studies (Box 210)
  - Mudimbe, V.Y.: Mestizo Space, 1999-2002 (Box 256)
  - Mudimbe, V.Y.: Nations, Identities, Cultures, 1996-1997 (Box 144)
  - Muehlmann, Shaylih; Where The River Ends, 2010-2012 (Box 109)
  - Muehlmann, Shaylih; Where The River Ends; Permissions, 2012 (Box 109)
  - Muel-Dreyfus, Francine: Vichy and the Eternal Feminine, 1996-2002 (Box 180)
  - Mullen (Box 291)
  - Muller, Carol: Musical Echoes, 2006-2011 (Box 247)
  - Mullin, Molly: Culture in the Marketplace, 1994-2001 (Box 218)
  - Mumford, Jeremy; Vertical Empire, 2012 (Box 102)
  - Mungo Park, 1999-2002 (Box 301)
  - Munt, Sally: Butch/Femme, 1996-1997 (Box 210)
  - Muraco, Anna: Odd Couples, 2005-2012 (Box 253)
  - Murphy, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Murphy Michelle, 2004 (Box 272)
  - Murphy, Michelle; Seizing the Means of Reproduction, 2009-2012 (Box 102)
  - Murphy, Michelle; Seizing the Means of Reproduction; Art, 2012 (Box 102)
  - Murphy, Michelle; Seizing the Means of Reproduction; Contract, 2012 (Box 102)
  - Murphy, Michelle; Seizing the Means of Reproduction; Permissions, 2012 (Box 102)
  - Murray, Martin: City of Extremes, 2007-2011 (Box 232)
  - Murray, Martin: City of Extremes, 2004-2009 (Box 233)
  - Musil, 1990 (Box 330)
  - Myers, Ella; Democratic Politics and Care for the World, 2011-2013 (Box 109)
  - Myers, Ella; Democratic Politics and Care for the World; Contract, 2011-2012 (Box 109)
  - Myers, Natasha: Rendering Life Molecular, 2009-2015 (Box 367)
  - Naby, Eden: "Cabs", 1988 (Box 210)
  - Nadel, Alen: Containment Culture, 1992-1995 (Box 180)
  - Nadja Durbach, 2003 (Box 512)
  - Naficy, Hamid: A Social History of Iranian Cinema, 2005-2011 (Box 247)
  - Naficy, Hamid: A Social History of Iranian Cinema, Volume 3, 2005-2012 (Box 253)
  - Naficy, Hamid; A Social History of Iranian Cinema, 2004-2012 (Box 102)
  - Nair, Parvati: A Different Light, 2003-2012 (Box 253)
  - Najmabadi, Afsaneh; Sex-In Change, 2010-2013 (Box 114)
  - Najmabadi, Afsaneh; Sex-In Change; Permissions, 2011-2012 (Box 114)
  - Najmabadi, Afsaneh; Sex-In Change; Contract, 2011-2012 (Box 114)
  - Nan Keohane, 2004-2005 (Box 267)
  - Nancy Abelmann, 2006-2010 (Box 322)
  - Nancy Goodwin, 2004 (Box 282)
  - Nancy Mann, 1991-2004 (Box 297)
  - Nancy Triolo, 1991 (Box 329)
  - Nancy, Appelbaum, 2000-2002 (Box 265)
  - Naranch, Bradley; German Colonialiasm in a Global Age, 2010-2015 (Box 120)
  - Naranch, Bradley; German Colonialiasm in a Global Age; Permissions, 2013 (Box 120)
  - Nascar- Fixin to Git, 2002 (Box 265)
  - Nash, Jennifer C.; The Black Body in Ecstasy, 2010-2014 (Box 120)
  - Navaro-Yashin, Yael: The Make-Believe Space, 2008-2013 (Box 253)
  - Naylor, 1988-1989 (Box 330)
  - Naylor, Thomas: Downsizing the U.S.A., 1995 (Box 210)
  - Neal Devines, 2004 (Box 259)
  - Nealon, Christopher: Foundlings, 1997-2003 (Box 221)
  - Nealon, Jeffrey: Alterity Politics, 1997-1999 (Box 180)
  - Needham, 2004-2005 (Box 284)
  - Negar Mattahedeh, 2007-2008 (Box 300)
  - Negra, Diane; Gendering the Recession, 2011-2014 (Box 120)
  - Negra, Diane; Gendering the Recession; Art and Permissions, 2012-2014 (Box 120)
  - Negra, Diane; Gendering the Recession; Contracts, 2012-2013 (Box 120)
  - Negri Toni, 2004-2009 (Box 308)
  - Neil Whitehad, 2000-2006 (Box 293)
  - Neil Whitehead, 2000-2003 (Box 270)
  - Nelly Oudshoorn, 2001-2002 (Box 512)
  - Nelson, 1997-2000 (Box 345)
  - Nelson, Dana D and Russ Castronovo, 1999-2001 (Box 513)
  - Nelson, Dana: National Manhood, 1997-1999 (Box 148)
  - Nelson, Diane M.: Who Counts?, 2013-2015 (Box 367)
  - Nevin, Thomas: Ernst Junger and Germany, 1995-1998 (Box 210)
  - Newberg, Paula: New Directions in Telecommunications, 1988-1991 (Box 210)
  - Newitz, 1997-2003 (Box 272)
  - Newman, Robert: Transgressions of Reading, 1991-1993 (Box 210)
  - Newton, Esther: Margaret Mead Made Me Gay, 1997-2001 (Box 159)
  - Newton, Esther; Cherry Grove, Fire Island, 2011-2014 (Box 122)
  - Ngô, Fiona; Imperial Blues, 2012-2014 (Box 114)
  - Nguyen Tu, Thuy: The Beautiful Generation, 2006-2011 (Box 242)
  - Nguyen, Hoang Tan, 2010-2014 (Box 92)
  - Nguyen, Mimi Thi; The Gift of Freedom, 2004-2011 (Box 102)
  - Nguyen, Vinh-Kim: The Republic of Therapy, 2002-2012 (Box 233)
  - Ni Zhen, 1999-2001 (Box 301)
  - Ni, Zhen: Contract, c. 1999 (Box 302)
    Contract, and correspondence relating to, with Zhen Ni for Memiors from the Beijing Film Academy
  - Ni, Zhen: Memoirs from the Beijing Film Academy, 1998-2001 (Box 302)
  - Ni, Zhen: Memoirs from the Beijing Film Academy, 1998-2001 (Box 302)
  - Ni, Zhen: Memoirs from the Beijing Film Academy, 1998-2003 (Box 302)
  - Ni, Zhen: Memoirs from the Beijing Film Academy, 1999-2001 (Box 302)
  - Nicholas, 2000-2007 (Box 275)
  - Nicholas De Genova, 2000-2004 (Box 259)
  - Nicholas De Genova, 2004-2005 (Box 272)
  - Nicholas School Forums and Forests, 2003-2006 (Box 508)
  - Nichols, 1989 (Box 330)
  - Nickerson, Catherine: The Web of Iniquity, 1991-1999 (Box 151)
  - Nickson, Andrew and Lambert, Peter, eds.; The Paraguay Reader, 2009-2012 (Box 116)
  - Nijinska, Irina: Bronislava Nijinska, 1991-1992 (Box 210)
  - Nikitina, 1989-1990 (Box 330)
  - Nils Jacobsen, 2000 (Box 512)
  - Nimura, 1995-1999 (Box 351)
  - Nimura, Kazuo: The Ashio Riot of 1907, 1995-1998 (Box 211)
  - Nordloh, David: American Literary Scholarship, 1989-1991 (Box 136)
  - Nordloh, David: American Literary Scholarship, 1994-1996 (Box 256)
  - Nordstrom, Karl: Living with the New Jersey Shore, 1984-1986 (Box 211)
  - Norindr, Panivong: Phantasmic Indochina, 1994-1998 (Box 143)
  - Norris, Christopher: Reclaiming the Truth, 1995-1996 (Box 146)
  - Norton, Barbara Gheith, Jehanne: An Improper Profession, 1995-2001 (Box 130)
  - Novak, David; Music at the Edge of Circulation, 2007-2013 (Box 109)
  - Nugent, Daniel: Rural Revolt in Mexico, 1995-2000 (Box 180)
  - Nugent, Neill: Government and Politics of the European Union, 1993-1998 (Box 136)
  - Nugent, Neill: Government and Politics of the European Union, 1991-2001 (Box 152)
  - Nugent, Richard: Gay Rebel of the Harlem Renaissance, 1991-2002 (Box 180)
  - Nugent, Richard: Gay Rebel of the Harlem Renaissance, 1997-2002 (Box 224)
  - Nuhall, 2004-2005 (Box 284)
  - Nulo, Nagtsang; Permissions, 2012-2014 (Box 92)
  - Nuttall, 2006-2007 (Box 300)
  - Oan Cook, 1998-2006 (Box 511)
  - O'Brien, Anthony: Against Normalization, 1994-2001 (Box 215)
  - O'Brien, William Arctander: Novalis, 1993-1996 (Box 303)
  - Ocberg, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Ochoa Gautier, Ana Maria; Contract, 2007-2013 (Box 92)
  - Ochoa, Marcia; Queen for a Day, 2007-2014 (Box 120)
  - O'Connor, Erin: Raw Material, 1999-2000 (Box 180)
  - Odets, Walt: In the Shadow of the Epidemic, 1994-2000 (Box 141)
  - O'Donnell, Patrick: Latent Destinies, 1993-2001 (Box 214)
  - O'Dougherty, Maureen: Consumption Intensified, 1998-2002 (Box 180)
  - O'Faarrell, Mary Ann: Telling Complexions, 1994-1996 (Box 211)
  - O'Farrell, 1994-1999 (Box 345)
  - O'Hara, Matt and A. Fischer: Imperial Subjects and Race and Identity in Colonial Latin America, 2005-2008 (Box 306)
    Proposal, reader reports, and correspondence regarding Imperial Subjects and Race and Identity in Colonial Latin America
  - Okada, Richard: Japanese Literature, 1990-1992 (Box 303)
    Proposal, reader reports, internal records, and correspondence relating to Tale of the Genji
  - Okeke-Agulu, Chika, 2012-2014 (Box 92)
  - Olcott, 2003-2008 (Box 281)
  - Olick, Jeffrey, 2001-2003 (Box 277)
  - Olivares, Jorge; Areanas of Desire, 2011-2012 (Box 109)
  - Olivares, Jorge; Areanas of Desire; Permissions, 2011-2012 (Box 109)
  - Olson, Jan: Hitchock a la Carte, 2007-2015 (Box 361)
  - O'Malley, 1978-1985 (Box 342)
  - Oneil, 2003 (Box 272)
  - O'Neill, Kevin and Thomas, Kedron: Securing the City, 2008-2010 (Box 240)
  - Ong, Aihwa: Asian Biotech, 2007-2010 (Box 233)
  - Ong, Aihwa: Flexible Citizenship, 1996-2001 (Box 149)
  - Orin Starn, 1997-1999 (Box 511)
  - Orthner, 2004-2005 (Box 274)
  - Ortiz, Fernando: Cuban Counterpoint, 1993-2000 (Box 141)
  - Ortner, Sherry B.; Not Hollywood, 2011-2013 (Box 109)
  - Ossman, Susan: Three Faces of Beauty, 1998-2002 (Box 225)
  - Ottolenghi, 1991 (Box 330)
  - Owens, Louis: American Literary Scholarship, 1989-1994 (Box 136)
  - Oyama, Susan: Evolution's Eye, 1997-2001 (Box 156)
  - Oyama, Susan: The Ontogeny of Information, 1997-2002 (Box 156)
  - Padilla, 2004-2007 (Box 300)
  - Padunov, Vladimir: Dostoevsky's the Devils, 1988-1996 (Box 211)
  - Pagano, 1987 (Box 346)
  - Page, 2005-2008 (Box 316)
  - Paige west, 2002-2004 (Box 272)
  - Painting the Universe, 1990-1994 (Box 317)
  - Palmer, Christopher Dick, Philip, 1997 (Box 211)
  - Palmer, Steven: From Popular Medical to Medical Populism, 1996-2002 (Box 180)
  - Palmer, Steven; State of Ambiguity, 2011-2013 (Box 120)
  - Palmer, Steven; State of Ambiguity; Permissions, 2013 (Box 120)
  - Palmie, Stephan: Wisards and Scientists, 1999-2001 (Box 180)
  - Palmore, 1983-1985 (Box 330)
  - Palmore, 1980-1983 (Box 341)
  - Palmore, 1986-1988 (Box 346)
  - Palumbo-Lin, David; The Deliverance of Others, 2009-2012 (Box 102)
  - Palumbo-Liu, David Robbins, Bruce and Tanoukhi, Nirvana: Immanuel Wallerstein and theProblem of the World, 2005-2011 (Box 240)
  - Pamela Wilson, 2005-2008 (Box 304)
  - Panagia, 2003-2005 (Box 281)
  - Pandey Sharma, 2005-2009 (Box 327)
  - Pandian, Anand: Reel World, 2013-2015 (Box 367)
  - Pane, 1998-2001 (Box 338)
  - Pane, Fray: an Account of the Antiquities, 1996-2001 (Box 151)
  - Pang, Laikwan: Creativity and Its Discontents, 2008-2012 (Box 254)
  - Park, Mungo: Travels in the Interior Districts of Africa, 1997-1999 (Box 302)
  - Parker, Andrew: The Theorist's Mother, 2010-2012 (Box 254)
  - Parker, Deborah: Commentary and Ideology, 1991-1995 (Box 211)
  - Parker, Harold T.: Three Napoleonic Battles, 1982-1984 (Box 318)
  - Parrinder, Patrick: Learning from Other Worlds, 1999-2002 (Box 221)
  - Parssinen, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Partin, 1968-1978 (Box 342)
  - Patch, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Patell, Cyrus: Negative Liberties, 1998-2001 (Box 195)
  - Patinkin, Don: Essays On and In the Chicago Tradition, 1978-1981 (Box 211)
  - Patinlein, 1975-1989 (Box 321)
  - Patinlein, 1978-1988 (Box 341)
  - Paton, Diana and Forde, Maarit: Obeah and Other Powers, 2010-2011 (Box 254)
  - Patrick Johnson, 2001-2003 (Box 282)
  - Patrick Weil, 2007-2008 (Box 305)
  - Patterson, Annable: Fables of Power, 1990-1991 (Box 211)
  - Patterson, Daniel Zugg, Charles: Arts in Earnest, 1988-1990 (Box 135)
  - Patterson, Daniel: Sound of the South, 1992-1994 (Box 211)
  - Patton, Cindy and Sanchez-Eppler, Benigno: Queer Diasporas, 1993-2003 (Box 155)
  - Patton, Cindy: Fatal Advice, 1993-1996 (Box 211)
  - Patton, Peter: Conneticut Shore, 1987-1991 (Box 211)
  - Paul Greenough, 2000-2002 (Box 520)
  - Paulakos, 1988-1989 (Box 330)
  - Paulson, 1995-1999 (Box 351)
  - Paulson, Ross: Liberty, Equality, and Justice, 1993-1997 (Box 180)
  - Payne, Leigh Unsettling Accounts, 2004-2006 (Box 508)
  - Peach, 1975-1983 (Box 340)
  - Pean Jod, 2007-2009 (Box 332)
  - Peard, Julyan: Race, Place, and Medicine, 1996-2000 (Box 181)
  - Pearson: Multinational Corporations and 3rd World Environments, 1985-1987 (Box 318)
  - Pease & Wiegman (Box 265)
  - Pease, Donald, 1992-1994 (Box 303)
    Proposal, reader reports, internal records, and correspondence relating to National Identities and Post-Americanist Natives and Revisionist Interventions into the Americanist Canon
  - Pecknold, Diane; Hidden in the Mix, 2008-2013 (Box 109)
  - Pecknole, Diane, 2003-2006 (Box 508)
  - Pefanis, Julian: Heterology and the Postmodern, 1988-1992 (Box 211)
  - Peformance Practice, 1986-2001 (Box 286)
  - Pei-Chan Lan, 2002-2003 (Box 267)
  - Pelley Patricia, 2000-2001 (Box 265)
  - Peloso, Vincent: Contested Plantations, 1996-1999 (Box 149)
  - Perelman, Michael: Classical Political Economy, 1988-1998 (Box 155)
  - Perelman: Invention of Capitalism, 1993-2001 (Box 303)
  - Perez, 1984-1987 (Box 319)
  - Perez, Gustavo Firmat: Do the Americas Have a Common Literature?, 1986-1989 (Box 318)
  - Perez, Gustavo Firmat: Literature and Liminality, 1984-1985 (Box 318)
  - Perez-Firmat, Gustavo: Idle Fictions, 1992-1994 (Box 212)
  - Permissions for Close Reading, eds. Lentricchia and DuBois, 2000-2002 (Box 269)
  - Permissions; Burton, A and I. Hofmeyr; Ten Books that Shaped the British Empire, 2011-2014 (Box 89)
  - Perrone, Charles: Seven Faces, 1994-1996 (Box 181)
  - Perry Duncan (Box 319)
  - Perry, Duncan: Macedonian Revolutionary Organization, 1986-1987 (Box 318)
  - Perry, Duncan: Polish Encyclopedia Project (Box 318)
    List of Polish encyclopediae and CV
  - Perry, John: Translationsof Sadriddin Ayniny's Memoirs, 1987 (Box 212)
  - Perry, Marc: Negro Soy Yo, 2007-2015 (Box 367)
  - Perry, Pamela: Shades of White, 1998-2004 (Box 225)
  - Pessar, 2001-2003 (Box 280)
  - Peter Fens, 1996-2000 (Box 513)
  - Peter Law, 2003-2004 (Box 268)
  - Peter Paris, 2004-2009 (Box 326)
  - Peter Winn, 1998-2003 (Box 267)
  - Peterson, Dale: Up from Bondage, 1996-1999 (Box 181)
  - Peterson, Dale: Up From Bondage, 1997-2000 (Box 215)
  - Peterson, Jennifer Lynn; Education in the School of Dreams, 1998-2013 (Box 110)
  - Peterson, Kristin; Spectacular Markets, 2012-2014 (Box 92)
  - Peyser (Box 337)
  - Peyser (Box 338)
  - Peyser, Thomas: Utopia and Cosmopolis, 1994-1999 (Box 181)
  - Pfaff, 2004-2006 (Box 281)
  - Pfaffenberger, Bryan: Anthropology of Technology, 1986-1991 (Box 212)
  - Pfau, Thomas: Lessons of Romanticism, 1997-1998 (Box 181)
  - Pfister Joel, 2005-2008 (Box 316)
  - Pfister Noel, 2001-2009 (Box 260)
  - Pham, Minh-Ha: Asians Wear Clothes on the Internet, 2008-2015 (Box 368)
  - Philipsen, Dirk: We Were the People, 1991-1992 (Box 212)
  - Phillips & Miller, 1973-1986 (Box 347)
  - Photo, 1996 (Box 344)
    Reviews, correspondence, and marketing materials for Art Song in America
  - Picard, Dane: Living With the Great Salt Lake, 1985 (Box 212)
  - Picato Pablo (Box 322)
  - Piccato, Pablo: City of Suspects, 1998-2001 (Box 181)
  - Pickering, 2004-2006 (Box 300)
  - Piglia, Ricardo: Artificial Respiration, 1991-2001 (Box 303)
    Reader reports, media, internal records, and correspondence
  - Piglia, Ricardo: The Absent City, 1997-2001 (Box 214)
  - Pilkey, 1995-2003 (Box 337)
  - Pilkey, 1995-2003 (Box 338)
  - Pilkey Jr., Orrin: The North Carolina Shore and it's Barrier Islands, 1997 (Box 181)
  - Pilkey, Joanne: Currituck to Calabash, 1982-1988 (Box 212)
  - Pilkey, Orin and Cooper, Andrew; Contract, 2014 (Box 92)
  - Pilkey, Orin and Cooper, Andrew; Permissions, 2013-2014 (Box 92)
  - Pilkey, Orin and Cooper, Andrew; The Last Beach, 2013-2014 (Box 92)
  - Pilkey, Orrin and Pilkey, Keith: Global Change, 2009-2011 (Box 247)
  - Pilkey, Orrin: Living with the Shore Series, 1979-1990 (Box 181)
  - Pirandello, Luigi: Her Husband, 1996-2002 (Box 214)
  - Plotnitsky, Arkady: Complementarity, 1992-1994 (Box 212)
  - Pluhar, Evelyn: Beyond Prejudice, 1994-1995 (Box 199)
  - Polan Dana, 2005-2008 (Box 316)
  - Polan, Dana: Julia Child's The French Chef, 2006-2011 (Box 247)
  - Polar, Antonio Cornejo; Writing in the Air, 2011-2012 (Box 105)
  - Pollock, Anne; Medicating Race, 2010-2012 (Box 102)
  - Pollock, Anne; Medicating Race; Contract, 2011 (Box 102)
  - Pollock, Sheldon: Forms of Knowledge in Early Modern Asia, 2004-2010 (Box 241)
  - Polt, John: San Camilo, 1936, 1990-1998 (Box 131)
  - Polvinen, Tuomo: Imperial Borderland, 1994-1995 (Box 141)
  - Pomorska, Krystyan: Jakobsonian Poetics and Slavic Narrative, 1987-1992 (Box 212)
  - Pond, Wayne: Soundings, 1996 (Box 181)
  - Poniatowska, Elena: Hasta no Verte Jesus Mio, 1997-1998 (Box 212)
  - Popkin, Jeremy: Bicentennial Reflections, 1987 (Box 212)
  - Popkin, Jeremy: Revolutionary News, 1986-1990 (Box 212)
  - Popkin, William: Statutes in Court, 1997-1999 (Box 181)
  - Porter, 1965-1975 (Box 347)
  - Porter, Eric: The Problem of the Future World, 2004-2010 (Box 233)
  - Portis (Box 317)
  - Portis-Winner, Irene: Semiotics of Peasants in Transition, 1991-2002 (Box 225)
  - Post Communism, 1997-1998 (Box 337)
  - Post Communism, 1997-1998 (Box 338)
  - Post, Robert: Prejudicial Appearances, 2000-2001 (Box 222)
  - Poster, 2003 (Box 284)
  - Poteat, William: Polanyian Meditation's, 1984-1989 (Box 212)
  - Potts, Jason; Theory Aside, 2011-2014 (Box 121)
  - Potts, Jason; Theory Aside; Permissions, 2012-2013 (Box 121)
  - Pottsm Jason; Theory Aside; Contracts, 2011-2013 (Box 121)
  - Pound, Omar and Bob Spoo: Ezra Pound and Margaret Cravens, 1982-1987 (Box 320)
    Proposal, reader report, correspondence, media reports, and contract
  - Povinelli, 2003-2005 (Box 284)
  - Povinelli, Elizabeth: Economies of Abandonment, 2009-2011 (Box 247)
  - Povinelli, Elizabeth: The Cunning of Recognition, 1999-2003 (Box 225)
  - Powell, Jefferson: The Moral Tradition of American Constitutionalism, 1992-1994 (Box 212)
  - Powell, John Harris, Duchess, 1997 (Box 212)
  - Poyo, Gerald E.: Los Pinos Nuevos, 1987-1989 (Box 320)
  - Predmore, 19790-1981 (Box 342)
  - Predmore and Predmore: Antonio Machado translations, 1984-1989 (Box 320)
    Reader reports, correspondence, media reports
  - Prentice, Rachel; Bodies in Formation, 2009-2012 (Box 102)
  - Press, Daniel: Democratic Delemmas in the Age of Ecology, 1992-1997 (Box 212)
  - Price David, 2001-2002 (Box 260)
  - Price, Morgan: Dispatches from the Revolution, 1996-1997 (Box 181)
  - Price, Reynolds: Learning A Trade, 1997-2000 (Box 214)
  - Prieto, Rene: Body of Writing, 1997-1999 (Box 181)
  - Priya Jaikumar, 2005 (Box 267)
  - Puar, Jasbir, 2006-2007 (Box 508)
  - Pudoff, 2005-2009 (Box 322)
  - Pugh, Ronnie: Ernest Tubb, 1992-2002 (Box 181)
  - Pun Ngai, 1998-2006 (Box 270)
  - Purnell, 2000 (Box 338)
  - Purnell, Jennie -Popular Movements and State Formation in Revolutionary Mexico, 1997-1999 (Box 182)
  - Pye, Christopher: The Vanishing, 1999-2000 (Box 214)
  - Qian, Zhaoming: Orientalism and Modernism, 1994-1995 (Box 212)
  - Quayson, Ato, 2012-2015 (Box 92)
  - Quiroz, 1988-1989 (Box 330)
  - Quizar, Robin: My Turn to Weep, 1996 (Box 212)
  - Rabasa, Jose: Writing Violence on the Northern Frontier, 1997-2000 (Box 182)
  - Race Kane, 2005-2007 (Box 316)
  - Radcliffe, Sarah: Indigenous Women and the Contradictions of Development Modernities, 2010-2015 (Box 368)
  - Radding, 2002-2004 (Box 520)
  - Radding, Cynthia: Wandering Peoples, 1991-1999 (Box 182)
  - Rademacher, Anne: Reigning the River, 2007-2011 (Box 247)
  - Radhakrishnan, Smitha: Appropriately Indian, 2007-2011 (Box 241)
  - Rafael Campo, 2005-2007 (Box 284)
  - Rafael, Vicente: Contracting Colonialism, 1992-1996 (Box 212)
  - Rafael, Vincent: Contracting Colonialism, 1996-2001 (Box 214)
  - Ragussis, Michael: Figures of Conversion, 1994-1995 (Box 213)
  - Rai, Amit, 2006-2007 (Box 316)
  - Raibman Paige, 2003-2006 (Box 275)
  - Raikhel, Eugene; Addiction Trajectories, 2010-2013 (Box 110)
  - Rainsford, Marcus; An Historical Account of the Black Empire of Hayti, 2008-2013 (Box 110)
  - Rajan (Box 338)
  - Rajan, Balachandra: Undern Western Eyes, 1993-1999 (Box 182)
  - Rajan, Kaushik: Lively Capital, 2006-2012 (Box 255)
  - Raleigh, Donald: A Russian Civil War Diary, 1983-1991 (Box 212)
  - Rama, Angel (Translator); Contract, 2008-2010 (Box 102)
  - Rama, Angel: The Lettered City, 1994-2002 (Box 146)
  - Rama, Claudio; Contract, 2009-2011 (Box 102)
  - RamaSwamy, 2006 (Box 322)
  - Ramberg, Lucinda, 2010-2014 (Box 92)
  - Rambuss, Richard: Closet Devotions, 1997-1998 (Box 149)
  - Ramet, Pedro: Catholicism and Politics in Communist Societies, 1985-1996 (Box 133)
  - Ramet, Pedro: Eastern Christianity and Politics in the Twentieth Century, 1985-1990 (Box 133)
  - Ramet, Pedro: Religion and Nationalism in Soviet and East European Politics, 1982-1988 (Box 134)